{
    "subject": "resource/Bonerama",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Bonerama is from United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9658468961715698,
            "question": "Is Bonerama a band from the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7690024375915527,
            "question": "Where is Bonerama from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7644284963607788,
            "question": "Is Bonerama an American band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6613276600837708,
            "question": "What is the country of origin for Bonerama?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6563458442687988,
            "question": "Where did Bonerama originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6284202337265015,
            "question": "To which nation does Bonerama belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6009998321533203,
            "question": "In which country was Bonerama formed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5841856598854065,
            "question": "What country is Bonerama associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5796956419944763,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Bonerama?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30669763684272766,
            "question": "Where are Bonerama's musical origins?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Bonerama is from United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9025_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nationality of Bonerama?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9025_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is Bonerama associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9025_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which country was Bonerama formed?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9025_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9025_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9025_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9025_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9025_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9025_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9025_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9025_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9025_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9025_94.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9025_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that according to the context information, none of the documents mention that Bonerama is from the United States. In fact, all the documents explicitly state that Bonerama is a band from New Orleans, which is implied to be in Louisiana, USA, but more specifically associated with the city's music scene, suggesting a strong connection to the culture and traditions of New Orleans rather than the US as a whole."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple mentions that Bonerama is a New Orleans-based band, and New Orleans is located in the United States. Therefore, it supports the statement that Bonerama is from the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The text states Bonerama is a brass funk rock band from New Orleans.  New Orleans is located in the United States.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information explicitly states \"1: Country of origin: New Orleans\" which is a city located in the United States, indicating that Bonerama is indeed from the United States.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}